grosh.com 2010-12-30

# We Rent Theatrical Backdrops, Curtains and Draperies for All Themes: Privacy Policy_broff

| Privacy Policy  
---  
  
  * Our Commitment to Privacy.  This notice describes our Privacy Policy.  Our privacy policy is designed to advise you about how we collect, use, and protect the personal information you provide.  _**By visiting[www.grosh.com](http://www.grosh.com/), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**_
  *  **What Information is Collected.**

    *  **Information You Provide to Us:**   We collect any information you enter on our web site as well as information that you provide to us in any other manner.  You can choose not to provide certain information to us, but you may not be able to take advantage of our services and features if you choose not to provide such information.
    *  **Automatic Information:  ** When you visit a web site, you disclose certain information, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time of your visit.  This web site, like many other web sites, records this basic information about visits to our web site.
    *  **Cookies** :  Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to your computer from a web server.  Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or to refuse to accept cookies.

  *  **How and When the Information is Used.**   The information we collect is used for administering our business activities.  Occasionally we may use the information to notify you about changes to our web site, new services, or special offers.
  *  **How We Protect Your Information.**   The privacy and protection of your information is important to us.  We do not make any personal information available to third parties without your permission.  If your access to any services and/or content is password protected, we advise that you do not disclose your password to anyone.  Also, we recommend that you sign out of a password-protected service at the end of your session.
  *  **Who Has Access to the Information.**   Information about our users is important to us.  We will not disclose any individually identifiable information to any third party without first receiving that user’s permission.
  *  **Methods We Use to Protect Your Information.**   We use security software to protect the confidentiality of your personal information.  In addition, our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information.  Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons.
  *  **Children.**   This web site does not provide services or sell products to children under the age of 18.
  *  **How You Can Access Your Information.**   You can request access to all your personal identifiable information by sending an e-mail to [info@grosh.com](mailto:info@grosh.com).
  *  **Consent.**   By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.
  *  **Changes to Privacy Policy.**   If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our web site.  Any such changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated in the change.
  *  **Effective Date.**   This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 28, 2007.
